[
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "01_Grace_Goodbye_WW",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@01_Grace_Goodbye_prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@01_Grace_Goodbye_a_new",
		"AchievementUnlock": "01_Grace_Goodbye_WW"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "01_Grace_Goodbye_MB",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@01_Grace_Goodbye_prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@01_Grace_Goodbye_a_new",
		"AchievementUnlock": "01_Grace_Goodbye_MB"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "01_Grace_Goodbye_WW_Final",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@01_Grace_Goodbye_next2_prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@01_Grace_Greet_04_a",
		"RequiredAchievement": "01_Grace_Goodbye_WW"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "01_Grace_Goodbye_MB_Final",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@01_Grace_Goodbye_next2_prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@01_Grace_Greet_04_a",
		"RequiredAchievement": "01_Grace_Goodbye_MB"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "01_boarfeast_topicTime",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@01_boarfeast_topicTime_prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@01_boarfeast_topicTime_a"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "01_boarfeast_topicTime_MB",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@01_boarfeast_topicTime_prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@01_boarfeast_topicTime_a_MB"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "01_boarfeast_topicOrigin",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@01_boarfeast_topicOrigin_prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@01_boarfeast_topicOrigin_a"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "01_boarfeast_topicOrigin_MB",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@01_boarfeast_topicOrigin_prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@01_boarfeast_topicOrigin_a_MB"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "01_crewmates_topicCorrupted",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@01_crewmates_topicCorrupted_prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@01_crewmates_topicCorrupted_a"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "01_crewmates_topicCorrupted_MB",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@01_crewmates_topicCorrupted_prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@01_crewmates_topicCorrupted_a_MB"
	}
]